everything that I mean I'm
literally everywhere
off to a rough start kids that I
world
myanna Grande and the
inspiration for my beef exam
shades was the good girl vibe
and the bad girls vibe everybody
has a little bit of both in them
so i wanted to express that with
these colors one hundred percent
of the proceeds are going to the
MAC AIDS son like every single
penny go to people infected with
HIV and AIDS that need medicine
food
no other brand does that so that
makes it ten thousand times more
exciting to me
all i got it does you credit it
I thought is that you provide
for a cat
you're credited with bringing
back the thigh high boots and I
am well thank you
tell us about those wicked boots
why I hi I don't know I think
they just look super hot and
everyone along getting cool
Thank You account call I like
him I was part of your I don't
know what beauty trends do you
wish would come back and which
one do you wish you could ban
forever
I don't know I guess it'll
really wish anything could come
back because my style is so
dated any way that I I kind of
just where all the stuff i wish
you could come back anyway
I feel like fashion and makeup
and hair and music are all forms
of self-expression
I'm not trying to ban or bring
back anyone's trends whatever
you like works by vi con
I have three I well I have a
bunch but my top three I think
would be Maryland Audrey
and Madonna it tells about your
army influences why are you
drawn to the John
I don't know these are the kinds
of questions that like you don't
really have answers for like
maybe it came from a past life
or something I've been listening
to a lot of beetles lately
I love The Supremes and a like
the temptations older stuff
imogen heap is my all-time
favorite artist I also listened
to a lot of madonna and rihanna
and nicki minaj my favorite food
i have no idea i love job
raising and like hummus and
vegetables but I love medjool
dates happen
the weirdest heads on the work
for help don't put that pic when
i was telling anyone where boot
up again
lavender my free time and I go
the gym a lot i go running with
my friends we watch movies and
shop online
I have six dogs Coco to Lucifer
million Hannah man
blacks and serious what you're
serious
a seamless one superpower would
it be to read people's minds
that would be so great flash so
terrible and that we would like
to turn it off and on healing
powers would be dope too
they just move my favorite words
i don't think they can use any
of them in this interview
I want to do it again because I
started like this my fans can
get involved
my friends can get involved by
simply buying a lipstick or
gloss and you're helping an
incredible costs by a couple of
your friends family things you
know
it also smells really good at
product always smell really good
just a plus
just saying